[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110822pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "NN", "NNS", ",", "VBD", "NNS", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 2, "question": "Sara, if you can hear me, I know there's been problems with communication here, what is the latest there right now?", "question_tokens": ["Sara", ",", "if", "you", "can", "hear", "me", ",", "I", "know", "there", "'s", "been", "problems", "with", "communication", "here", ",", "what", "is", "the", "latest", "there", "right", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBZ", "VBN", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "RB", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "EX", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 3, "answer": "We were hearing loud booms, loud blasts, a lot of rapid gunfire.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "were", "hearing", "loud", "booms", ",", "loud", "blasts", ",", "a", "lot", "of", "rapid", "gunfire", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mohammed Gadhafi"]}, "docId": "110822pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBZ", "IN", ",", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "NN", "IN", ",", "NNP", ":", "CD", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", ":", "JJ", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 22, "question": "Is that right?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 23, "answer": "Well, what we are hearing from the rebels is that, yes, they had hold of all three of the sons and now, they're saying hold on, Mohammed -- one of his sons -- Mohammed Gadhafi has escaped.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "what", "we", "are", "hearing", "from", "the", "rebels", "is", "that", ",", "yes", ",", "they", "had", "hold", "of", "all", "three", "of", "the", "sons", "and", "now", ",", "they", "'re", "saying", "hold", "on", ",", "Mohammed", "--", "one", "of", "his", "sons", "--", "Mohammed", "Gadhafi", "has", "escaped", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Libya"]}, "docId": "110822pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", ",", "IN", "CD", "NN", "WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "RB", "RB", "RBR", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "VBG", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 61, "question": "Do you actually believe that either of these sons were ever in proper custody or were we just spun a yarn here?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "actually", "believe", "that", "either", "of", "these", "sons", "were", "ever", "in", "proper", "custody", "or", "were", "we", "just", "spun", "a", "yarn", "here", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "NN", "NN", "CC", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 62, "answer": "Yes, it's difficult to say in this place, isn't it, because one correspondent who's been here much longer than me said that, you know, the thing is about Libya, the trouble with reporting it is that lying is the national sport.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "it", "'s", "difficult", "to", "say", "in", "this", "place", ",", "is", "n't", "it", ",", "because", "one", "correspondent", "who", "'s", "been", "here", "much", "longer", "than", "me", "said", "that", ",", "you", "know", ",", "the", "thing", "is", "about", "Libya", ",", "the", "trouble", "with", "reporting", "it", "is", "that", "lying", "is", "the", "national", "sport", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Tripoli"]}, "docId": "110822pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 78, "question": "Do you think he's still there?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "he", "'s", "still", "there", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 79, "answer": "Well, I think the capital of Tripoli is mostly under the control of the revolutionary forces.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "the", "capital", "of", "Tripoli", "is", "mostly", "under", "the", "control", "of", "the", "revolutionary", "forces", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110822pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBG", "IN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 94, "question": "What do you make of what's going on?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "make", "of", "what", "'s", "going", "on", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "WP", "POS", "VBG", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 95, "answer": "Well, obviously, there is a lot of confusion, a lot of misinformation going on here.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "obviously", ",", "there", "is", "a", "lot", "of", "confusion", ",", "a", "lot", "of", "misinformation", "going", "on", "here", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Gadhafi"], "LOCATION": ["Tripoli"]}, "docId": "110822pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "DT", "NNP", "VBZ", "NN", "TO", "RB", "VB", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "VB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 113, "question": "Do you feel that Moammar Gadhafi's position is basically over and we're just watching the beginning of the end?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "feel", "that", "Moammar", "Gadhafi", "'s", "position", "is", "basically", "over", "and", "we", "'re", "just", "watching", "the", "beginning", "of", "the", "end", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 114, "answer": "SLAN: It's hard to imagine a scenario whereby the Gadhafi loyalists manage to actually regain control over Tripoli, let alone over the entire country.", "answer_tokens": ["SLAN", ":", "It", "'s", "hard", "to", "imagine", "a", "scenario", "whereby", "the", "Gadhafi", "loyalists", "manage", "to", "actually", "regain", "control", "over", "Tripoli", ",", "let", "alone", "over", "the", "entire", "country", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Moammar Gadhafi"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Libya", "Egypt"]}, "docId": "110822pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "JJS", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "IN", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 119, "question": "What is going to happen in Libya to reassure the world that we're actually into a better situation for Libyan people?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "going", "to", "happen", "in", "Libya", "to", "reassure", "the", "world", "that", "we", "'re", "actually", "into", "a", "better", "situation", "for", "Libyan", "people", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "DT", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJR", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 120, "answer": "And the situation, of course, is much worse in Libya than it was in Egypt where you had at least the centralized military that could really form the backbone of a post-revolutionary society.", "answer_tokens": ["And", "the", "situation", ",", "of", "course", ",", "is", "much", "worse", "in", "Libya", "than", "it", "was", "in", "Egypt", "where", "you", "had", "at", "least", "the", "centralized", "military", "that", "could", "really", "form", "the", "backbone", "of", "a", "post-revolutionary", "society", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Libya"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110822pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBZ", "IN", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 126, "question": "Can you see a situation where if it gets completely out of control, though, the Americans will have to go in more harder and more people on the ground?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "you", "see", "a", "situation", "where", "if", "it", "gets", "completely", "out", "of", "control", ",", "though", ",", "the", "Americans", "will", "have", "to", "go", "in", "more", "harder", "and", "more", "people", "on", "the", "ground", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", ",", "DT", "NNPS", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "JJR", "NN", "CC", "JJR", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 127, "answer": "Under no circumstances is that going to happen.", "answer_tokens": ["Under", "no", "circumstances", "is", "that", "going", "to", "happen", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110822pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "IN", ",", "PRP", "CC", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 135, "question": "Do you have any credence to those kinds of reports?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "have", "any", "credence", "to", "those", "kinds", "of", "reports", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 136, "answer": "Yes, we've talked about this before, you and I.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "we", "'ve", "talked", "about", "this", "before", ",", "you", "and", "I", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERCENT": ["80 percent"], "LOCATION": ["Tripoli"]}, "docId": "110822pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "IN", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "CD", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 143, "question": "When is Gadhafi going to be gone, do you think, looking at the situation as it is now?", "question_tokens": ["When", "is", "Gadhafi", "going", "to", "be", "gone", ",", "do", "you", "think", ",", "looking", "at", "the", "situation", "as", "it", "is", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "NNP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "VBN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 144, "answer": "I mean with the rebels in control of from what I understand some 80 percent of the capital city of Tripoli, it's only a matter of time.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "mean", "with", "the", "rebels", "in", "control", "of", "from", "what", "I", "understand", "some", "80", "percent", "of", "the", "capital", "city", "of", "Tripoli", ",", "it", "'s", "only", "a", "matter", "of", "time", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Gadhafi"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110822pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 169, "question": "Were you disheartened to hear that two of Gadhafi's sons, having been in some form of custody, are now liberated again and are no longer in custody?", "question_tokens": ["Were", "you", "disheartened", "to", "hear", "that", "two", "of", "Gadhafi", "'s", "sons", ",", "having", "been", "in", "some", "form", "of", "custody", ",", "are", "now", "liberated", "again", "and", "are", "no", "longer", "in", "custody", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "IN", "CD", "IN", "NNP", "POS", "NNS", ",", "VBG", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "RB", "CC", "VBP", "DT", "JJR", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 170, "answer": "Well, this is a very fluid situation.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "this", "is", "a", "very", "fluid", "situation", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Gadhafi"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Moammar Gadhafi"], "LOCATION": ["U.S."]}, "docId": "110822pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "TO", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "NN", "CC", "NN", "PRP", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NNP", ":", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "CC", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 184, "question": "If you had a choice in the way that the American SEALs had a choice with Osama bin Laden of killing Moammar Gadhafi or bringing him back to justice, which would you prefer?", "question_tokens": ["If", "you", "had", "a", "choice", "in", "the", "way", "that", "the", "American", "SEALs", "had", "a", "choice", "with", "Osama", "bin", "Laden", "of", "killing", "Moammar", "Gadhafi", "or", "bringing", "him", "back", "to", "justice", ",", "which", "would", "you", "prefer", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NN", "NNP", "IN", "VBG", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "VBG", "PRP", "RB", "TO", "VB", ",", "WDT", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 185, "answer": "Moammar Gadhafi should be brought to justice and I think that it's important that the U.S. government does not try to broker a deal to find him asylum or grant him immunity, but he should be adjudicated either in the Libyan -- in the Libyan judicial system that needs to be revamped or with the international criminal court.", "answer_tokens": ["Moammar", "Gadhafi", "should", "be", "brought", "to", "justice", "and", "I", "think", "that", "it", "'s", "important", "that", "the", "U.S.", "government", "does", "not", "try", "to", "broker", "a", "deal", "to", "find", "him", "asylum", "or", "grant", "him", "immunity", ",", "but", "he", "should", "be", "adjudicated", "either", "in", "the", "Libyan", "--", "in", "the", "Libyan", "judicial", "system", "that", "needs", "to", "be", "revamped", "or", "with", "the", "international", "criminal", "court", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Moammar Gadhafi"], "LOCATION": ["Osama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110822pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 202, "question": "Are you questioning by judgment or what?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "questioning", "by", "judgment", "or", "what", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "CC", "WP", "."], "aSentId": 203, "answer": "I'm already questioning your judgment.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "already", "questioning", "your", "judgment", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["United States"]}, "docId": "110822pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNPS", "."], "qSentId": 216, "question": "What is the Jon Huntsman for America?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "the", "Jon", "Huntsman", "for", "America", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 217, "answer": "Preeminence with the United States.", "answer_tokens": ["Preeminence", "with", "the", "United", "States", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jon Huntsman"], "LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110822pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 223, "question": "Can it be the same as it used to be?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "it", "be", "the", "same", "as", "it", "used", "to", "be", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 224, "answer": "Of course.", "answer_tokens": ["Of", "course", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110822pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNP", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 225, "question": "Or should the American dream be slightly reinvented for the modern world?", "question_tokens": ["Or", "should", "the", "American", "dream", "be", "slightly", "reinvented", "for", "the", "modern", "world", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "MD", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "VB", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 226, "answer": "The American dream is the same.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "American", "dream", "is", "the", "same", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["China", "China", "America"]}, "docId": "110822pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "TO", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", ",", "JJ", "CC", "JJ", ",", "RB", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 236, "question": "Why try to build something like they did the last generation?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "try", "to", "build", "something", "like", "they", "did", "the", "last", "generation", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "NN", "TO", "VB", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 237, "answer": "And you were in China for a couple of years and you well know that when you compared bureaucracy in China to bureaucracy in America, one of the reasons that they are marching on, good or bad, whatever your view of it, is they are not consumed with red tape over every tiny thing they do.", "answer_tokens": ["And", "you", "were", "in", "China", "for", "a", "couple", "of", "years", "and", "you", "well", "know", "that", "when", "you", "compared", "bureaucracy", "in", "China", "to", "bureaucracy", "in", "America", ",", "one", "of", "the", "reasons", "that", "they", "are", "marching", "on", ",", "good", "or", "bad", ",", "whatever", "your", "view", "of", "it", ",", "is", "they", "are", "not", "consumed", "with", "red", "tape", "over", "every", "tiny", "thing", "they", "do", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["China"]}, "docId": "110822pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "VBN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 239, "question": "But does America have a fundamental problem businesswise with the sheer volume of paperwork, red tape, legalese, stuff that I believe slows down modern business?", "question_tokens": ["But", "does", "America", "have", "a", "fundamental", "problem", "businesswise", "with", "the", "sheer", "volume", "of", "paperwork", ",", "red", "tape", ",", "legalese", ",", "stuff", "that", "I", "believe", "slows", "down", "modern", "business", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "NNP", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBD", "NN", ",", "JJ", ",", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 240, "answer": "In an autocratic system like China, there's plenty of red tape.", "answer_tokens": ["In", "an", "autocratic", "system", "like", "China", ",", "there", "'s", "plenty", "of", "red", "tape", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110822pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 250, "question": "Other than people saying you're boring?", "question_tokens": ["Other", "than", "people", "saying", "you", "'re", "boring", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "IN", "NNS", "VBG", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 251, "answer": "I'll disabuse them of that real fast.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'ll", "disabuse", "them", "of", "that", "real", "fast", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110822pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 266, "question": "What values did he instill in you?", "question_tokens": ["What", "values", "did", "he", "instill", "in", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NNS", "VBD", "PRP", "MD", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 267, "answer": "Hard work.", "answer_tokens": ["Hard", "work", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110822pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 278, "question": "What was the name of your band?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "the", "name", "of", "your", "band", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 279, "answer": "Well, we had a lot of bands.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "we", "had", "a", "lot", "of", "bands", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Marie"]}, "docId": "110822pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "CC", "NNP", "VBD", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 292, "question": "Did you see a potential conflict arising had you pursued your dream?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "see", "a", "potential", "conflict", "arising", "had", "you", "pursued", "your", "dream", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBG", "VBD", "PRP", "VBN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 293, "answer": "Donnie and Marie did OK.", "answer_tokens": ["Donnie", "and", "Marie", "did", "OK", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Beefheart"]}, "docId": "110822pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 295, "question": "Now is that true?", "question_tokens": ["Now", "is", "that", "true", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 296, "answer": "If you can tell me anything about Captain Beefheart, I'll give you an answer.", "answer_tokens": ["If", "you", "can", "tell", "me", "anything", "about", "Captain", "Beefheart", ",", "I", "'ll", "give", "you", "an", "answer", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110822pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 316, "question": "Do you want to get your hands dirty in the grubbiness of running for high office and all that comes with it?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "want", "to", "get", "your", "hands", "dirty", "in", "the", "grubbiness", "of", "running", "for", "high", "office", "and", "all", "that", "comes", "with", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NNS", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "DT", "DT", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 317, "answer": "We've come this far.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "'ve", "come", "this", "far", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110822pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 332, "question": "Are you comfortable that they're ready?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "comfortable", "that", "they", "'re", "ready", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 333, "answer": "They have been raised in a public milieu, a public environment.", "answer_tokens": ["They", "have", "been", "raised", "in", "a", "public", "milieu", ",", "a", "public", "environment", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110822pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 341, "question": "Why is that and how do you change that?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "is", "that", "and", "how", "do", "you", "change", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "IN", "CC", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 342, "answer": "Well, it's early days.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "'s", "early", "days", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["August"]}, "docId": "110822pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 346, "question": "When is the point when we should look at how you're performing and properly judge you?", "question_tokens": ["When", "is", "the", "point", "when", "we", "should", "look", "at", "how", "you", "'re", "performing", "and", "properly", "judge", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "CC", "RB", "NN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 347, "answer": "Not August.", "answer_tokens": ["Not", "August", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110822pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 361, "question": "You really want to get me in trouble, do you?", "question_tokens": ["You", "really", "want", "to", "get", "me", "in", "trouble", ",", "do", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "JJ", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 362, "answer": "I do, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110822pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "JJS", "NNS", ",", "IN", "RB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 382, "question": "What's the one that you would say to a friend over dinner?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "the", "one", "that", "you", "would", "say", "to", "a", "friend", "over", "dinner", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "CD", "WDT", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 383, "answer": "I don't -- well, I tell you what I've told most people, if not everybody.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "--", "well", ",", "I", "tell", "you", "what", "I", "'ve", "told", "most", "people", ",", "if", "not", "everybody", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110822pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "CC", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 412, "question": "Do you have sympathy for him in the position he found himself in, where you have such an intransigent part of the republican party really just refusing to compromise?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "have", "sympathy", "for", "him", "in", "the", "position", "he", "found", "himself", "in", ",", "where", "you", "have", "such", "an", "intransigent", "part", "of", "the", "republican", "party", "really", "just", "refusing", "to", "compromise", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 413, "answer": "He appointed me and I stood up and took the appointment to serve my country.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "appointed", "me", "and", "I", "stood", "up", "and", "took", "the", "appointment", "to", "serve", "my", "country", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110822pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 431, "question": "Where would you disagree with her?", "question_tokens": ["Where", "would", "you", "disagree", "with", "her", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "."], "aSentId": 432, "answer": "Well, on the debt ceiling.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "on", "the", "debt", "ceiling", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110822pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 442, "question": "On gay marriage?", "question_tokens": ["On", "gay", "marriage", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 443, "answer": "Yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110822pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 452, "question": "What is your view of abortion?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "your", "view", "of", "abortion", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 453, "answer": "I am pro-life.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "am", "pro-life", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110822pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ",", "NN", "CC", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 463, "question": "Do you think there are any circumstances where you would think an abortion is acceptable?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "there", "are", "any", "circumstances", "where", "you", "would", "think", "an", "abortion", "is", "acceptable", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "WRB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 464, "answer": "Rape, incest and life of the mother would be the exceptions that I could live with.", "answer_tokens": ["Rape", ",", "incest", "and", "life", "of", "the", "mother", "would", "be", "the", "exceptions", "that", "I", "could", "live", "with", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110822pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 465, "question": "When you see, again, intransigence by some of the -- particularly the Tea Party end of the Republican party on this kind of thing, do you think again that it's bordering on bigotry?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "see", ",", "again", ",", "intransigence", "by", "some", "of", "the", "--", "particularly", "the", "Tea", "Party", "end", "of", "the", "Republican", "party", "on", "this", "kind", "of", "thing", ",", "do", "you", "think", "again", "that", "it", "'s", "bordering", "on", "bigotry", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", ",", "NN", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", ":", "RB", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 466, "answer": "All I have to say -- I don't have a lot of patience on a lot of the non-economic issues.", "answer_tokens": ["All", "I", "have", "to", "say", "--", "I", "do", "n't", "have", "a", "lot", "of", "patience", "on", "a", "lot", "of", "the", "non-economic", "issues", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110822pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 478, "question": "Would you endorse what he said?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "you", "endorse", "what", "he", "said", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 479, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110822pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 493, "question": "Do you like him?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "like", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 494, "answer": "I don't know him that well.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "him", "that", "well", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110822pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "RP", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 505, "question": "But what you're basically doing is knifing him straight in the back, aren't you?", "question_tokens": ["But", "what", "you", "'re", "basically", "doing", "is", "knifing", "him", "straight", "in", "the", "back", ",", "are", "n't", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "VBZ", "VBG", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 506, "answer": "I'm just pointing out the facts.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "just", "pointing", "out", "the", "facts", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "110822pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 513, "question": "But what I'm saying is you clearly have it in you?", "question_tokens": ["But", "what", "I", "'m", "saying", "is", "you", "clearly", "have", "it", "in", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 514, "answer": "I'm glad to get your endorsement, Piers.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "glad", "to", "get", "your", "endorsement", ",", "Piers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110822pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "MD", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 526, "question": "Could you ever imagine running as a running mate to someone like Mitt Romney?", "question_tokens": ["Could", "you", "ever", "imagine", "running", "as", "a", "running", "mate", "to", "someone", "like", "Mitt", "Romney", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "TO", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 527, "answer": "There would be too many jokes about that.", "answer_tokens": ["There", "would", "be", "too", "many", "jokes", "about", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mitt Romney"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110822pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "NN", "WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", ":"], "qSentId": 529, "question": "What about to a Tea Party candidate?", "question_tokens": ["What", "about", "to", "a", "Tea", "Party", "candidate", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "IN", "TO", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 530, "answer": "You know, anyone who is going to --", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "anyone", "who", "is", "going", "to", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Tea Party"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110822pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 533, "question": "Could you countenance such an idea?", "question_tokens": ["Could", "you", "countenance", "such", "an", "idea", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 534, "answer": "Captain Beefheart music, I assume you're talking.", "answer_tokens": ["Captain", "Beefheart", "music", ",", "I", "assume", "you", "'re", "talking", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Congress"]}, "docId": "110822pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "VBZ", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "NNS", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "CC", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 558, "question": "Shouldn't they be rewarded with a seat at the right hand?", "question_tokens": ["Should", "n't", "they", "be", "rewarded", "with", "a", "seat", "at", "the", "right", "hand", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "RB", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 559, "answer": "Everybody knows -- I think they're rewarded by people who they elect and put into Congress.", "answer_tokens": ["Everybody", "knows", "--", "I", "think", "they", "'re", "rewarded", "by", "people", "who", "they", "elect", "and", "put", "into", "Congress", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110822pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 560, "question": "You wouldn't rule out Michele Bachmann?", "question_tokens": ["You", "would", "n't", "rule", "out", "Michele", "Bachmann", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "RP", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 561, "answer": "I'm not playing the name game at all.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "not", "playing", "the", "name", "game", "at", "all", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michele Bachmann"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110822pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "RB", "VBZ", "RB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 580, "question": "What is the situation?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "the", "situation", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 581, "answer": "The situation now is pretty calm.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "situation", "now", "is", "pretty", "calm", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]